Now, we give the Israelis 95%
of our defense secrets. You want the
F-35? Done. Here's the F-35. You want
this advanced missile? Here you go. It's
on us. So, they steal the remaining 5%.
>> Which um spy force around the world did
you think was the most
impressive?
>> Oh, the Israelis.
>> Really?
>> Yeah. The Israelis have no rules.
John Kiryaku, the CIA whistleblower,
just exposed the dark and sinister
reality of Israeli Mossad, the
intelligence service. And what he talks
about here is just mindblowing given the
duplicity of the intelligence service of
America's greatest ally overseas. He
gets into the ruthless methods that
Mossad uses and has used historically,
not only to perpetuate madness and
murder, but also to steal from the
United States. So, let's see what he has
to say about this. Please like the video
and subscribe to the channel.
>> They'll kill anybody. Uh, what was it 3
years ago? This uh this pager operation.
>> Oh, it was so fascinating.
>> Good lord. It was It was a work of
genius.
>> It is genius. It is.
>> It was totally illegal.
>> Totally illegal.
>> But it was genius. The the moving parts.
>> I I didn't believe it was real. I had to
like re I was like there's no way that
this is real. This is the stuff of
movies.
>> It is.
>> For anyone that doesn't know what was
the story.
>> Ah yeah. Okay. So [snorts] the Israelis
knew that Hezbollah, the terrorist group
Hezbollah from Lebanon was communicating
using pagers. They didn't want to use
cell phones because they didn't want the
Israelis to intercept their phone calls.
And they thought, "Oh, pagers, those are
safe." So the Israelis
bought a company in like Hungary, I
think it was, that made pagers
and they got Hezbollah to order the
pagers from this company.
They were able to insert explosives in
the pagers and the pagers went to like
Taiwan and from Taiwan to Thailand and
then from Thailand to I forget where,
Syria, I guess. and then from Syria to
Lebanon.
And so what the Israelis did was they
were able to activate the explosives in
all the pagers simultaneously,
>> killing people.
>> They killed everybody of any import.
They essentially decapitated Hezbollah.
And then the ones they didn't kill in
that operation,
they bombed the apartment buildings
where they lived. See, this is the thing
too about the Israelis. If they want to
kill you, they won't
they won't like just do a close-in hit.
They'll blow up the entire city block
where you live. Yeah, it's pretty
indicative of what they did in Gaza,
too. Essentially having no problem
killing lots of women and children there
with babies plucked up from the rubble
using US technology to do it. Palunteer
algorithms sorting between those who
will live and die. And yeah, this was
genius in its propensity to murder mass
numbers of people, including innocent
people near where the pagers went off.
That included children and innocents
that weren't involved in Hezbollah. And
despite them doing this, they still use
the existence of Hezbollah, despite the
fact that, as Kiryaku said, they've been
decapitated to propagandize for regime
change in Iran like they're doing right
now. We can't allow the Iranian regime
to stand because they fund Hezbollah,
which we propagandized as having been
dismantled by our operation, but we're
still using it as an excuse for regime
change, for greater Israel, for genocide
in Gaza, etc. That's what the Israelis
do. They'll kill a thousand people just
to get you, and they don't care. And
then then they say, "What are you going
to do about it? You going to go to the
International Court of Justice?"
>> Do they do they really do this? Yeah.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And Kiryaku is right. They're not going
to run to the International Court of
Justice. They have an arrest warrant for
Netanyahu. But the United States will
back the Israelis and the genocidal head
of state freak that is at the top of
that regime no matter what and refuse to
give the Palestinians a state. They're
not going to do anything. They can get
away with this. The US will cover for it
even when the Israelis act against the
interests of you and me. The criminal
regime is tied together at the hip with
the Israelis and as John Mirshimer says,
I think appropriately that Israel is an
albatross around our neck. Did
>> did you ever interact with them?
>> Yes.
>> And how did you find them to be
>> miserable?
My very first briefing that I ever gave
as a junior analyst was to the Israelis.
My boss said, okay, he says, you're
going to give your first classified
liaison briefing. So, it's going to be
the Israelis and there are a couple
things you should know. I said, "Okay."
He said, "We don't allow the Israelis
into the building
ever." I said, "Why not?" He said,
"Because they spy on us." Not only do
they spy on us, they would always bring
gifts like, "Oh, we brought this
wonderful gift for you and you every
every time somebody tries to bring
something in, you have to x-ray it and
it's got like listening devices and it's
packed with two years worth of
batteries." We're like, "You guys, you
have to stop doing this. Every time you
come here, you try to bug our conference
rooms. You It's bad form. You have to
stop doing it." And then they're like,
"Oh, okay. Okay. We knew you would find
it. We're just kidding. Come on." Yeah.
Bad form. This is America's greatest
ally that spies on us. And then there's
never any repercussions, never any
ramifications. There's never any threat
to withdraw funding. And instead, the US
government, no matter who's elected
president, some more than others, it's
all relative, still backs this regime
despite doing that. And then you have
them laughing in our faces about it. And
meeting with Jonathan Pard, the
convicted Israeli spy that sold out
secrets, some of which included nuclear
secrets to the Israelis, which were
passed on to the Soviets in the Cold
War. Enough is enough. This stuff is
treacherous. It's deep. It's dark. It's
sinister. And that's an understatement.
So, we have to meet them miles away from
headquarters in a place that we rent.
So,
he said, "Nothing over the secret level.
No top secret information, just up to
secret." I'm like, "Okay." So, I go with
like a dozen analysts. And because I'm
the junior most analyst, I've only been
on the job at this point, I'm going to
say six weeks or so, I went last. So the
first analyst says, "I'm the chief
analyst and this is my briefing." And
then the next guy says, "I'm the
political analyst and I'm the econ
analyst and I'm the military analyst and
I'm the oil analyst and you know the
tech analyst and it comes to me." So I
said because I was overt at the time I
was not undercover. I said, "My name is
John Kuryaku and I'm going to brief you
on Saddam Hussein's psychological state
of mind."
Well, there were two Israelis there. One
was from Mossad and one was from
Shinbet. Shinbet is the FBI of Israel
and Mossad is the CIA of Israel. So the
Shinbet guy, he has his glasses down
like this and he he he goes like this.
He says, "Spell your name."
So I spell it Kir. I spell it and he
goes, "You are
Jewish." I said, "Don't you dare. I am
not recruitable. Don't you dare even try
it.
>> Just think about that. This is their
methodology trying to recruit people on
that basis to do the bidding of this
foreign intelligence service. Even doing
it to intelligent off intelligence
officers within the United States. I
mean, it's like thank heavens we have
people with integrity that came out of
the CIA and spilled these secrets like
John Kiryaku cuz we don't get them
otherwise. and whatever you want to say
about his past, man. He blew the cover
off CIA torture programs and thankfully
helped put an end to that, at least
ostensively. We're told that it's never
happened since then. But it's because of
Kiryaku and heroes like him and other
whistleblowers that came from the
intelligence circles at great risk to
themselves telling these secrets like
Edward Snowden as well. And they ruined
their lives. Why? Not because they lied,
but because they told the truth. Tell a
lie and you could become president. Tell
the truth and your public enemy number
one.
>> I was furious. We went out of the
briefing. I was going to explode.
Everybody started laughing at me.
They're like, "They do that to every one
of us." Every one of us.
>> They try and recruit you.
>> Yeah.
>> To turn against the United States.
On my very first day at the CIA, we got
a briefing from the CIA's director of
security and he said that all of us have
to have in the very front of our minds
the concept of counter intelligence. For
example, he said there's a steakhouse
right down the road on Route 123. It's
the it's the nearest restaurant to the
CIA. He goes, don't ever eat there. Why?
Because the KGB thinks we all eat there.
So all the customers are KGB officers
waiting for CIA people to walk in and
start talking about work. Don't ever eat
there. I've never eaten there to this
day
>> because they're potentially all Russian
spies.
>> So he said, "Our Israeli friends have
two officers in their embassy, one from
Mossad, one from Shinbet. The FBI has
identified
187 undeclared Israeli intelligence
officers spread all across the United
States, mostly at defense contractors
trying to steal our secrets. Now, we
give the Israelis 95%
of our defense secrets. You want the
F-35? Done. Here's the F-35. You want
this advanced missile? Here you go. It's
on us. So they steal the remaining 5%.
>> Just think about that. And all the
propaganda that Americans receive and
have received, you know, since our
birth, at least since I was born, that
Israel is our greatest ally, you know, a
beacon of democracy amongst a sea of
totalitarian regimes in the Middle East.
Not exactly true, but what is told to us
and that we have to support them at all
costs. This is what they're doing.
They're trying to recruit our
intelligence officers, trying to steal
our secrets. Some of them go beyond
that. They do succeed in stealing the
secrets. Even when they're captured,
there must be many more than just
Jonathan Pard. But Jonathan Pard was
indicted, charged, and convicted of that
crime. And then when he's freed, guess
what happens? Is he shunned by our
greatest ally in the Middle East? No.
He's welcomed with a red carpet.
Literally welcomed at the tarmac when he
was sent back. When his probation was
ended during, I believe, the first Trump
administration went back to Israel. On
which flight? The Adlesen's flight.
Sheldon and Miriam Adlesen's private jet
brought him back to Israel where he was
greeted on the tarmac by who? Benjamin
Netanyahu. America's greatest ally.
Right. No, a genocidal freak that treats
him like a hero. The Lakudnik treat pard
like a hero. Hero. A convicted spy that
sold the US out. It's just a total
embarrassment. It's a humiliation ritual
to go through this all the time and just
make excuses for this terrorist regime
that's tying my country up and our
soldiers up and all this bloodshed in
the Middle East complicity in those
empire building schemes that doesn't
serve the patriotic nature of the troops
that serve in that theater. No, it
serves the banks and the
military-industrial complex and APEC and
all the propagandists that want regime
change operations in Iran right now,
just like they wanted them in Syria and
Libya, in Afghanistan, in Iraq, etc. to
destabilize the regime, allow for the
Greater Israel project, the expansion of
Israel's borders, and a genocide in
Gaza. All to do what? To prevent the
enactment of a Palestinian state, what
Benjamin Netanyahu has always staked his
political career on. all for that. Well,
I'm glad for people like Kirayaku again
that tell the truth about these things
reveal the true sinister underbelly of
Mossad. And this is not to, you know,
put the CIA or any other intelligence
service in good light. The CIA should be
eradicated itself. It should be
abolished. It's criminal. It conducts
psychological operations to propagandize
us into wars and try to enact mind
control experiments in MK Alter or
control our media like Operation
Mockingbird to overthrow foreign
regimes, gain Americans more enemies and
in result more dead bodies, more
bloodshed, more debt, more inflation,
more curtailment of our civil liberties
like in the form of the Patriot Act and
the DHS and the TSA. All that is what we
get from this twisted relationship.
Well, I think he puts it on blast here.
I'm glad for this interview. Really
interesting segment the whole interview
was. And I do want to hear what you guys
have to say. Is Mossad brilliant in
terms of its madness and murder? Is it
like the most sinister intelligence
service in the world because of lack of
any ethics whatsoever? That's what
Kiryaku thinks. What do you think? Put
it down in the comments down below. Like
the video. Subscribe to the channel.
Subscribe to Diary of a CEO. Good
interview for sure. Also, if you like
this video, please consider joining as a
YouTube member. You can do that by
clicking the join button down below. If
you do that, you'll gain immediate
access to all my videos before they go
live to the general public on YouTube.
You'll be able to see my membersonly
videos right away. There's usually like
four or five or six at any one time. You
can see them right away if you join, and
I really appreciate your support. Also,
if you want a free copy of my first
book, Compact of the Republic, go down
to the description, click the link
there, and you just plug in your email,
and I'll send you a free PDF copy of
that full book, free of charge, no
obligation, just cuz I appreciate you
watching. And look, I have a few demands
of the regime. They're simple. I don't
apologize for them. It's no more war, no
more debt, no more inflation, and no
more empire. Peace out, guys. Catch you
in the next one.